JAMUNA V

B.A MUSIC (VOCAL), DMT, ECCED

Through all of my musical experience I have learned to be disciplined, detail – oriented, and creative in my artistic endeavors. Singing has taught me a significant amount about the art of performance and the necessary confidence and poise that accompanies it. My years of weekly voice lessons have also built my classical voice techniques and taught me the skills to be regimented in my practice.

vinumavinujanu@gmail.com

9789217779

15 A, Nanjappa Gounder Layout,Bharathi road, Telugupalayam Pudur, Coimbatore, India

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

SSLC (2014)

Vasavi Vidhyalaya Matric Hr Sec School, Coimbatore.

HSSC (2016)

Corp. SRP Ammani AmmalGirl's Hr Sec School, Coimbatore.

B.A MUSIC (VOCAL) (2019)

Tamilnadu Music College.

DMT (MUSIC) (2020)

Tamilnadu Music College.

ECCED (2022)

Safal Institute, Mumbai.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Music Teacher

Music Teacher in Pencil kids Institute.

11/2023 - Present

Music Teacher

Music Teacher in Orchids International School, Mahalakshmi Layout, Bangalore.

05/2023

Vocal Teacher (online)

Working as a Vocal Teacher in GO4GURU from

01/2021 - Present

Vocal Teacher(online)

Working as a Vocal Teacher in GROW IN STEPS from

11/2021 - Present

SKILLS

Carnatic Music.

Veena & keyboard.

ORGANIZATIONS

7 Tones Music Institute, Coimbatore.

Rotaract Club of Coimbatore uptown.

CERTIFICATES

Certification in UCMAS (Abacus Mental Arithmetic Program).

Certification in C Programming - IECD (Bharathidasan University).

LANGUAGES

Enalish

Full Professional Proficiency

Tamil

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Art

Music

Singing